const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'What is the space between one place and another called?',
        answer: ['Distance']
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'What is used to find the distance between two places on a map?',
        answer: ['Map Scale']
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'What helps us know what direction we need to go on a map?',
        answer: ['Compass Rose']
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: `What's the symbol on the map stand for?`,
        answer: ['Map Key']
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What are the lines that go East to West called?',
        answer: ['Latitude Lines']
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What are the lines that go North to South called?',
        answer: ['Longitude Lines']
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What are real or artificial lines that separate geographic areas like countries, states, and cities called?',
        answer: ['Borders']
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What tells us about the map?',
        answer: ['Title']
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'What is 0 degress latitude called?',
        answer: ['Equator']
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'What is 0 degrees longitude called?',
        answer: ['Prime Meridian']
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: 'Name the seven continents',
        answer: ['North America', 'South America', 'Africa', 'Asia', 'Europe', 'Antarctica', 'Australia']
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: `Name the five borough's of New York City?`,
        answer: ['Queens', 'Brooklyn', 'Manhattan', 'Staten Island', 'Bronx']
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: 'Name the Cardinal Directions?',
        answer: ['North', 'East', 'South', 'West'] // Never Eat Soggy Waffles
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: 'Name the intermediate directions?',
        answer: ['Northeast', 'Southeast', 'Southwest', 'Northwest']
    }
]